<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ManHood</string>
    <string name="choose_your_gender">CHOOSE YOUR GENDER</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">By continuing you agree to the Terms of Use and you acknowledge that you have read the
        Privacy Policy
    </string>
    <string name="enter">ENTER</string>
    <string name="world">World</string>
    <string name="area">Area</string>
    <string name="hood">Hood</string>
    <string name="your_result">Your Results</string>
    <string name="manhood">ManHood</string>
    <string name="certificate_save_to_photo_library">Save to Photo Library</string>
    <string name="empty_row_value">---</string>
    <string name="length">LENGTH:</string>
    <string name="thickness">THICKNESS:</string>
    <string name="thickest_at">THICKEST AT:</string>
    <string name="curvature">CURVATURE:</string>
    <string name="date_of_issue">DATE OF ISSUE:</string>
    <string name="device">DEVICE:</string>
    <string name="manhood__">ManHood --</string>
    <string name="how_to_guide">HOW TO GUIDE</string>
    <string name="step_1">STEP 1</string>
    <string name="step_1_description">Sit in front of a mirror</string>
    <string name="step_2">STEP 2</string>
    <string name="step_2_description">Wear a white/blue/green/black T-shirt</string>
    <string name="step_3">STEP 3</string>
    <string name="step_3_description">Take off the cover</string>
    <string name="step_4">STEP 4</string>
    <string name="step_4_description">Press the phone to the bone</string>
    <string name="step_5">STEP 5</string>
    <string name="step_5_description">Make sure the edges of the phone and your manhood are as visible as possible
    </string>
    <string name="ready_male_title">Ready to Go</string>
    <string name="ready_female_title">That’s how to do it</string>
    <string name="ready_male_description">I got it! Time to measure!</string>
    <string name="ready_female_description">This is the way for guys to digitally measure themselves</string>
    <string name="settings">SETTINGS</string>

    <string name="hide_personal_data">Hide Personal Data</string>
    <string name="units">Units</string>
    <string name="join_the_inner_circle">Join the Inner Circle</string>
    <string name="give_feedback">Give Feedback</string>
    <string name="tell_a_friend">Tell a friend</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="privacy">Privacy</string>
    <string name="privacy_caps">PRIVACY POLICY</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use">Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_caps">TERMS OF USE</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy_text" formatted="false">This Privacy Policy explains the information that The ManHood Team (\&quot;ManHood,\&quot;
        \&quot;we,\&quot; or \&quot;us\&quot;) collect about users of the \&quot;ManHood\&quot; mobile application and
        related
        services, how we use that
        information, and with whom we share it. If we make any material changes to our privacy practices, we will post a
        revised Privacy Policy on this page. If you have any questions, please contact us by sending an email to
        help@manhoodapp.com.\n

        \n<b>We strive to not collect any personally identifiable information</b>\n

        \n
        <b>Information we collect automatically:</b>
        When you use ManHood, we automatically collect and store information
        about your mobile device. This information includes:\n
        \t<b>•</b>\t Your installation of ManHood. We only register the device and not your personal data.\n
        \t<b>•</b>\t Your mobile device’s geographic location while the app is actively running\n
        \t<b>•</b>\t Technical information about your mobile device (such as type of device and operating system)\n
        \t<b>•</b>\t How long you are using ManHood and which services and features you used\n

        \n
        <b>Information you choose to provide:</b>
        In order to use all functions of ManHood, you can be asked to make
        measurements using the app. For development purposes we may store the pictures used to extract these
        measurements. We strive to have the highest security and ethical standard and at all time guard and facilitate
        these material, meaning that material and install information such as location is kept separated. In order to
        use ManHood you are asked to inform us about your sex. Other information might be required and might be public
        to others where you are represented in an anonymous group.
        <b>We do not store information like:</b>
        your name, address,
        email address, or phone number.

        \n
        <b>How we use your information:</b>
        We use your information to provide and improve our services. Your information
        will be public for other users in an anonymous group based on geographical location or other data provided by
        you.\n

        \n
        <b>Use of your information by others:</b>
        We may share user information with other companies for various reasons as
        described below. What information we make available to other companies depends on the nature of our relationship
        with them. We generally require these other companies to keep users\&apos; information confidential.\n
        <b>Science and Research institutions:</b>
        We may share all types of information for research purposes.\n
        <b>Advertisers:</b>
        We may allow advertisers and advertising networks to collect information about your mobile device,
        activities, and geographical location to include targeted ads to you.\n
        <b>Analytics Companies:</b>
        We may allow analytics companies to use tracking technologies to collect information about
        our users\&apos; devices and online activities. These companies analyze this information to help us understand
        how our
        service is being used.\n
        <b>Aggregated Information:</b>
        We may publicly disclose aggregated information about our users, such as making info
        graphics about average measurements per area in a city.\n
        <b>Legal matters:</b>
        We may disclose any information: in response to a legal request, such as a subpoena, court order,
        or government demand; to investigate or report illegal activity; or to enforce our rights or defend claims. We
        may also transfer your information to another company in connection with a corporate restructuring, such as a
        sale or merger.\n

        \n
        <b>Children\&apos;s privacy:</b>
        We do not allow persons under 18 to use this service, and we do not knowingly
        collect any
        personally identifiable information from persons under the age of 13.\n

        \n
        <b>Information from users outside the United States</b>
        If you\&apos;re outside the United States, your information
        will
        be
        sent to and stored in the United States, where our servers are located. By using ManHood, you agree to the
        information collection, use, and sharing practices described in this Privacy Policy.\n
    </string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_text">
        <b>PLEASE READ THIS DOCUMENT CAREFULLY</b>
        \n
        The ManHood Team (\&quot;ManHood,\&quot; \&quot;we,\&quot; or \&quot;us\&quot;)
        operates the ManHood mobile app and related services (\&quot;ManHood\&quot;). By using ManHood in any way, you
        accept these Terms of Service (\&quot;Agreement\&quot;). If you do not wish to be bound by this Agreement, do
        not use ManHood.
        \n

        \n
        <b>Contents</b>\n
        \t1. Who May Use ManHood
        \n
        \t2. License to Use ManHood
        \n
        \t3. Privacy
        \n
        \t5. Term and Termination; Account Deletion
        \n
        \t6. Disclaimers
        \n
        \t7. Code of Conduct; Prohibited Activities
        \n

        \n
        <b>Who May Use ManHood</b>
        You must be at least 18 years old to use ManHood. Use is void where prohibited. By using
        ManHood, you represent and warrant that you have the right, authority and capacity to enter into this Agreement
        and to abide by all of the terms and conditions of this Agreement.
        \n

        \n
        <b>License to Use ManHood</b>\n
        ManHood grants you a limited, non-exclusive license to access and use ManHood for your
        own personal, non-commercial purposes. This license is personal to you and may not be assigned or sublicensed to
        anyone else.
        \n
        Except as expressly permitted by ManHood in writing, you will not reproduce, redistribute, sell, create
        derivative works from, decompile, reverse engineer, or disassemble ManHood. Nor will you take any measures to
        interfere with or damage ManHood. All rights not expressly granted by The ManHood Team are reserved.
        \n

        \n
        <b>Privacy</b>
        Your privacy rights are set forth in our Privacy Policy (Privacy Policy), which forms a part of this
        Agreement. We strive to not collect any personally identifiable information. Please review the Privacy Policy to
        learn about:
        \n
        \t◦ What information we may collect about you
        \n
        \t◦ What we use that information for
        \n
        \t◦ What third-party information, if any, you are agreeing to share by using ManHood; and
        \n
        \t◦ With whom we share that information
        \n

        \n
        <b>Term and Termination;</b>
        Account Deletion This Agreement begins on the date you first use ManHood and continues
        until terminated in accordance with the provisions hereof.
        \n
        The ManHood Team may suspend, disable, or delete your account (or any part thereof) if we determines that you have
        violated any provision of this Agreement or that your conduct or content would tend to damage ManHood’s
        reputation or goodwill.
        \n
        Upon termination, all licenses granted by The ManHood Team will terminate. In the event of account deletion for
        any reason, content that you submitted may no longer be available. The ManHood Team shall not be responsible for
        the loss of such content.
        \n

        \n
        <b>Disclaimers.</b>
        The ManHood Team provides ManHood on an \&quot;as is\&quot; and \&quot;as available\&quot; basis. You therefore
        use ManHood at your own risk. The ManHood Team expressly disclaims any and all warranties of any kind, whether
        express or
        implied, including, but not limited to the implied warranties of merchantability, medical, fitness for a
        particular purpose, non-infringement, and any other warranty that might arise under any law.
        \n

        \n
        <b>Code of Conduct.</b>
        \n\tBy using ManHood you acknowledge to follow the measurement instructions for accurate measurements.
        \n
        \tYou will not try to mislead, fool or exploit the measurement technology
        \n
        \tYou will not use any robot, spider, site search/retrieval application, or other manual or automatic device or
        process to retrieve, index, “data mine”, or in any way reproduce or circumvent the navigational structure or
        presentation of the Service or its contents.
        \n
        \tYou will not interfere with or disrupt the services or the site or the servers or networks connected to the
        services or the site.
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="fragment_support_header_text">Have any questions or comments?\nPlease help us improve ManHood</string>
    <string name="give_feedback_caps">GIVE FEEDBACK</string>
    <string name="support_email_address">hello@manhoodapp.com</string>
    <string name="send_a_support_email">Send a support email</string>
    <string name="fragment_help_header_text">Find help to use ManHood</string>
    <string name="measurement_taking_guide">Measurement taking guide</string>
    <string name="faq">Frequently asked questions</string>
    <string name="faqs_caps">FAQS</string>
    <string name="faq_text">
        <b>Who can see me?</b>
        \n
        No one can distinguish you from a group of people. You are always anonymous in the crowd.
        \n\n
        <b>What do the bars mean?</b>
        \n
        It is the distribution of the filtered location you have chosen: the World, the Area (the 200 closest in
        distance), or the Hood (the 20 closest in distance to where you are). Higher bars means more measurements with
        that measurement. It is called a histogram.
        \n\n
        <b>I get \&apos;Length\&apos; and \&apos;Thickness\&apos; but what is \&apos;Thickest at\&apos;?</b>
        \n
        \&apos;Thickest at\&apos; indicates the thickest point along the length. The base is 0, the tip is 1, and the
        middle is 1 2.
        Btw, thickness and girth are just synonyms.
        \n\n
        <b>My length is longer than my phone; will it work?</b>
        \n
        Yes. We look at the skin not the phone, which is why you need to be wearing a T-shirt.
        \n\n
        <b>Mine is quite bent, so the length will be shorter, right?</b>
        \n
        No. We are measuring in 3D by combining both the front and the side. That is why length is measured in three
        dimensions and also angle and girth.
        \n\n
        <b>Should it be hard when I measure?</b>
        \n
        You want to measure the maximum stats, right? Besides what\&apos;s the point in measuring the shape, like
        curvature,
        for something soft?
        \n\n
        <b>Do I really need a mirror to take my measurements?</b>
        \n
        Yes, it is the core of the technology.
        \n\n
        <b>How accurate are the measurements?</b>
        \n
        Following the guide gives high accuracy. We do some statistical approximation of thickness (girth) so please
        send us feedback if you think the algorithms can be improved. Remember, the less you cover your manhood with
        your fingers the more of the shaft can be measured.
        \n\n

        <b>What more can I do to make better measurements?</b>
        \n
        - Have good, even lighting
        \n
        - Try not to have bright spots on the skin
        nor shadows
        \n
        - Clean the mirror
        \n
        - Hold as little of you manhood as possible
        to show the most of the contour
        \n
        - Avoid contact with your hands and your
        manhood
        \n
        - Use one or two fingers
        \n\n
        <b>How can I communicate with the other users?</b>
        \n
        You are anonymous as are all other users, but take a look around you, you can probably spot the guys and girls
        in the cafe library bar club that have just checked you out.
        \n\n

        <b>I can\&apos;t see myself the \&apos;Your Result\&apos; button is gone</b>
        \n
        You have switched on \&quot;Hide Personal Data\&quot; in the settings. This is a great feature if you want to
        show
        the app
        to friends but not brag about your personal stats.
        \n\n

        <b>How do I cancel my subscription?</b>
        \n
        It\&apos;s cool to see the Hood and be in the Inner Circle, and you can always start seeing them again by
        joining
        the
        Inner Circle again. When you cancel your subscription is not renewed from next week. 
        Visit Google Wallet. Along the left side of your screen, select More >
		Subscriptions. Select Cancel subscription.
        \n\n

        <b>What information is registered?</b>
        \n
        We strive to not store any personally identifiable material.
        When you save the certificate with a username it is only for your photo album. It is never stored anywhere
        else.
        \n\n

        <b>This is silly?</b>
        \n
        Yes, but what is just for fun for you can actually be a serious thing for someone else. Your data is of great
        help for others. One of the most popular articles on Wikipedia is \&quot;Human Penis Size\&quot;. It\&apos;s
        read
        by tens of
        thousands of people every day. Use ManHood, even just for the fun of it, and you are helping guys around the
        world to see what is normal. You are contributing to our mission to uncover every little corner of the world. It
        may be a small thing for you but together we make a giant leap for ManKind Hood.
        \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="help_caps">HELP</string>
    <string name="server_link">https://www.shapeapptech1.com</string>
    <string name="room_for_improvements">Room for improvements</string>
    <string name="something_wasnt_right">Something wasn\'t right</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="tips">Tips</string>
    <string name="camera_caps">CAMERA</string>
    <string name="ref_shot">REF SHOT</string>
    <string name="front_shot">FRONT SHOT</string>
    <string name="side_shot">SIDE SHOT</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="analyze">Analyze</string>
    <string name="tap_to_take_picture">Tap to take a picture</string>
    <string name="move_and_size_image_to_fit_size">Move and size image to fit the %s size</string>
    <string name="ref_shot_info_dialog_title">Example of Reference Picture</string>
    <string name="front_shot_info_dialog_title">Example of Front Picture</string>
    <string name="side_shot_info_dialog_title">Example of Side Picture</string>
    <string name="got_it">Got it!</string>
    <string name="ref_adjustments_info_dialog_title">Example of Reference Adjustment</string>
    <string name="front_adjustments_info_dialog_title">Example of Front Adjustment</string>
    <string name="side_adjustments_info_dialog_title">Example of Side Adjustment</string>
    
    
    <string name="erd_title">Rate this app</string>
    <string name="erd_message">Hi, take a minute to rate this app and help support to improve more new features. ;)</string>
    <string name="erd_no_thanks">No, thanks</string>
    <string name="erd_remind_me_later">Remind me later</string>
	<string name="erd_rate_now">Rate now</string>
	
</resources>
